[Music]
hello everyone
i hope you're having a lovely day this
has not been the easiest year
especially for my country and in the
midst of the current turmoil i'm
reaching out to you
and hoping that together we can find a
moment of peace
enjoying nature and all the abundance it
gives us
as you can see that early snowfall
melted away as quickly as it came
but it will be back in this video i will
be answering a few more questions on
rural cottage living
since my channel has grown and i've
received many more inquiries on what
it's like to live out here
[Music]
one question i'm often asked is for
advice on how to make the move to the
countryside
and how exactly i did it myself
but i don't really know how to answer
these questions because i don't really
feel like an expert
and my story is so different from yours
that there is little advice i could give
that would apply to everyone's different
situations
all i will say is that anything is
possible with patience and perseverance
don't give yourself a timeline on when
to achieve a dream work towards it one
tiny step at a time
it may take years or even decades and
some creative thinking
but it can happen
[Music]
the people who live in my area come from
a variety of financial
and social backgrounds some like myself
rent tiny homes others live off-grid in
order to be able to afford land
i suppose the options are as limited or
varied as you decide they are
but most importantly my mission with
these videos is to highlight the magic
in daily life
in a way that can be applied wherever
you are not just the countryside
for me my environment is a great benefit
to my soul
but not the foundation of my joy i had
to work on myself and my spirituality to
find contentment
[Music]
another question i often get is about
isolation
wild animals and strangers for privacy
reasons i don't wish to film the other
homes in my area
but i'm not alone in the wilderness per
se and i have several neighbors within
walking distance
i need to drive about five miles to get
to my job
and i feel both remote yet able to
access what i need in town when i visit
as for dealing with animals in such a
rural place
predators are very wary of humans and it
is rare that they would show themselves
even more so that they would ever attack
the number of incidents every year is
very low
and i personally believe that by
choosing to live in a rural place it's
my responsibility to respect the animals
that live here
since they are the ones that are most
often attacked by us
and whose homes are taken away on a
related note
some people have expressed fear of
running into dangerous strangers walking
the wilderness
and i'd say that if you find anyone here
at all it's probably a friendly hiker or
a local
and it feels extremely safe
[Music]
lastly to those who have inquired about
me on a personal level i realized i've
never actually spoken my name here
it is paola and i'm turning 24 this
december
my boyfriend's name is luke and you will
no doubt meet him in a future video
i have two siblings who live and thrive
in cities
a sister named lyanna and my brother
rohan
who lives in australia i hope you can
meet them someday
they're one of my greatest sources of
pride and joy and love
[Music]
i hope this at least answered some of
your questions and feel free to ask me
more
as usual i've left all relevant links to
information
in the description bar that being said i
will now invite you to come with me
to a canyon near my home to take a deep
breath of crisp autumn air
to smell the pines and what earth and
let all your worries and fears
of the future to wash away with the
raindrops
no matter what happens externally you
have the power to cultivate contentment
and peace at this time in the world
things may seem polarized and angry and
confusing
but there is always hope and everywhere
there are good people
doing good things it's just a matter of
where you look
i'm sending you all my love and
encouragement on your own journey
comment and let me know how you're doing
i always love reading your messages
have a lovely day or night
[Music]
you